[
	{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "The characteristic of enantiomers is",
		"options": [
			"only that they are chemically identical",
			"only that they are mirror images of each other",
			"both (A) and (B)",
			"none of these"
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"categories": [
			"chemistry"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "The guardian of the Indian Constitution is the",
		"options": [
			"Supreme Court of India",
			"High Court",
			"President of India",
			"Prime Minister of India"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"political-science"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "Repeated Urination While Sleeping, even after five years of age is called",
		"options": [
			"Eneuresis",
			"Tic",
			"Stuttering",
			"Encopresis"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"biology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "In a certain code '253' means 'books are old', '546' means 'man is old' and '378' means 'buy good books'. What stands for 'are' in the code",
		"options": [
			"2",
			"4",
			"5",
			"6"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"logic"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "Atmospheric pressure is important in the process of",
		"options": [
			"Blood Flow",
			"Micturition",
			"Reproduction",
			"Breathing"
		],
		"answer": 4,
		"categories": [
			"general"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "In a certain code, if BHOPAL is written as EERMDI, then how will POWDER be written in the same code",
		"options": [
			"SLZAHO",
			"SRZGHU",
			"NMUBCP",
			"NRUGCU"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"logic"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "The permanent stopping of the menstrual cycle in women is called",
		"options": [
			"Menopause",
			"Menarche",
			"Dismenorrhea",
			"Amenorrhea"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"biology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "Which of the following vitamins is soluble in water",
		"options": [
			"Vitamin A",
			"Vitamin C",
			"Vitamin K",
			"Vitamin D"
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"categories": [
			"biology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "A is 40 metres south-west of B, C is 40 meters south-east of B, then C is in which direction from A",
		"options": [
			"South",
			"West",
			"East",
			"North-East"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"categories": [
			"logic"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "The Aligarh Muslim University was founded by",
		"options": [
			"Dr. Saifuddin Kichlu",
			"Sir Syed Ahmad Khan",
			"Mohmmad Ali Jinnah",
			"Maulana Mohammad Ali"
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"categories": [
			"history"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "11",
		"question": "Of the following, which is the most common site for metastasis in lung cancer",
		"options": [
			"Kidney",
			"Stomach",
			"Liver",
			"Spleen"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"categories": [
			"biology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "12",
		"question": "Express 45 minutes as a fraction of a day",
		"options": [
			"1/32",
			"1/40",
			"1/60",
			"1/24"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"mathematics"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "13",
		"question": "When are the chances of acute endometritis developing in a woman",
		"options": [
			"after menopause",
			"after menarche",
			"after abortion or childbirth",
			"in childhood"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"categories": [
			"biology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "14",
		"question": "Psychoanalytic Therapy was developed by",
		"options": [
			"Sigmund Freud",
			"Jacobson",
			"Franklin",
			"Aristotle"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"categories": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "15",
		"question": "What should be the temperature of water used for cold sponging",
		"options": [
			"98 F",
			"105 F",
			"70 F",
			"0 F"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"categories": [
			"nursing"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "16",
		"question": "A train running at a speed of 30 meters/sec crosses a platflorm 600 meters long in 30 seconds. The length of the train is",
		"options": [
			"120 meters",
			"150 meters",
			"200 meters",
			"300 meters"
		],
		"answer": 4,
		"categories": [
			"mathematics"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "17",
		"question": "Which of the following is not found in urine",
		"options": [
			"Only glucose",
			"Only protein",
			"Only Red blood cells",
			"All of the above"
		],
		"answer": 4,
		"categories": [
			"biology"
		]
	}
]